{
    "id": "654902a26f4949a5b2dd7d1cff078789",
    "title": "Simple present or present continous",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "e01c6ad5c2f74d18a204148c8484eac0",
            "title": "Simple Present Or Present Continuous Tense Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "My father ………………….. at a bank.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "work",
                        "works",
                        "is working"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "My brothers …………………. incredibly well.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "sing",
                        "sings",
                        "are singing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I always ………………… a bath before I go to bed.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "take",
                        "am taking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Supriya ………………… English well.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "speak",
                        "speaks",
                        "is speaking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ………………….. in the garden.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "work",
                        "works",
                        "is working"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘What are you doing there?’ ‘I …………………. a letter.’",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "write",
                        "am writing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The children …………………. a song.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "sing",
                        "are singing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Rohan ………………….. his car.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "repair",
                        "repairs",
                        "is repairing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The postman ………………….. the letters.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "bring",
                        "brings"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………. the answer.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "know",
                        "am knowing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}